{
    "subject": "resource/The_Cay",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The Cay is located in the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9707886576652527,
            "question": "Is The Cay in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8876270055770874,
            "question": "Where is The Cay located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.574176013469696,
            "question": "What country is The Cay in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41452765464782715,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks near The Cay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3499387800693512,
            "question": "What is the geography of The Cay like?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3024830222129822,
            "question": "What is the history of The Cay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28436440229415894,
            "question": "Is The Cay a popular tourist destination?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2286318838596344,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about The Cay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16946177184581757,
            "question": "What kind of climate does The Cay have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13244430720806122,
            "question": "Are there any unique cultural traditions associated with The Cay?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Cay is located in the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7485_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of climate does The Cay have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7485_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about The Cay?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7485_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is The Cay a popular tourist destination?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7485_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7485_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7485_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7485_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7485_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7485_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7485_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7485_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7485_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7485_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7485_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents contain information about a book called \"The Cay\", but they do not provide any evidence that it is located in the United States. In fact, the document with file_path \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7485/re-ranker-msmarco/109.txt\" suggests that The Cay is a locality located on Governor's Harbour, Bahamas."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information supporting that \"The Cay\" is located in the United States. Instead, they indicate it is a locality in Governor's Harbour, Bahamas, and also mention its location in the West Indies."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The Cay is located in the Bahamas, not in the United States.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The context states that The Cay takes place on the Dutch island of Curacao during World War II.  It also mentions that the West Indies includes various islands like Cuba, Jamaica, Haiti, Puerto Rico, Cura\u00e7ao, the Bahamas, Grenada, and the Virgin Islands.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The Cay has been mentioned as a locality located in Governor\u02bcs Harbour, Bahamas.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information indicates that \"The Cay\" refers to a locality in Governor's Harbour, Bahamas, not the United States.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}